(Bernadette:)You don't think she'd actually
send you something gross
(Bernadette:)or dangerous, do you?
(Penny:)I know one way
to find out... sniff this.
(Amy:)She's pregnant,
she's not a bloodhound.
(Bernadette:)Although I am getting
a little machine oil.
(Bernadette:)I think it's metal.
(Penny:)Come on, just open it.
(Raj:)You know,
on Game of Thrones,
(Raj:)Balon Greyjoy received
his son's genitals in a box.
(Penny:)Well, never hurts
to have a spare.
BERNADETTE:
What is that?
(Raj:)Wow. It's an antique sextant.
(Raj:)Sailors used these to find
their position by the stars.
(Amy:)What a nice gift
for an astrophysicist.
(Raj:)I know, she's so thoughtful.
(Penny:)See, she's trying
to get you back.
(Penny:)Now, that is exactly
what I would've gotten you
(Penny:)if I had any idea
what it is or what you do.
(Raj:)You know, I have too much
self-esteem to let this girl
(Raj:)guilt me into getting back
together with her.
(Amy:)You don't need to be pregnant
to smell that load of crap.